export const mongodbQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is MongoDB?",
      answer: "MongoDB is a NoSQL database management system."
    },
    {
      question: "What is BSON?",
      answer: "BSON is the binary representation of JSON-like documents used by MongoDB."
    },
    {
      question: "What is a document in MongoDB?",
      answer: "A document is a JSON-like data structure stored in MongoDB, representing a record in the database."
    },
    {
      question: "What is a collection in MongoDB?",
      answer: "A collection is a group of MongoDB documents. It is the equivalent of an RDBMS table."
    },
    {
      question: "What is a shard key?",
      answer: "A shard key is used for dividing data across multiple servers in a MongoDB sharded cluster."
    },
    {
      question: "What is the default port for MongoDB?",
      answer: "The default port for MongoDB is 27017."
    },
    {
      question: "What is the primary key in MongoDB?",
      answer: "The primary key in MongoDB is the '_id' field."
    },
    {
      question: "What is a replica set in MongoDB?",
      answer: "A replica set is a group of MongoDB servers that maintain the same data set, providing redundancy and high availability."
    },
    {
      question: "What is indexing in MongoDB?",
      answer: "Indexing in MongoDB is the process of creating indexes to improve query performance."
    },
    {
      question: "What is the aggregation framework in MongoDB?",
      answer: "The aggregation framework is a MongoDB feature that enables users to perform data aggregation operations on documents."
    }
  ];